affsession.com 2011-12-24

# Affiliate Marketing

**Last updated on October 15, 2009**

This is the Privacy Policy of the Appsession Inc. website (together with our affiliates and subsidiaries, “Appsession”, “we”, “us”, “our” and terms of similar meaning) and our related products and services (the “Site”). It describes the information that we collect from users of our Site (“Users”) as part of the normal operation of our Site, and how we use and disclose this information.

By accepting the Privacy Policy in registration or by visiting and using the Site, you expressly consent to our collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to our Terms of Use.

## How We Use Your Information

We use personal information in the file we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the Site, to provide to you the services offered by the Site; resolve service disputes; troubleshoot problems; measure consumer interest in our products and services, inform you about online and offline offers, products, services, events and updates; deliver information to you that, in some cases, is relevant to your interests, such as product news; customize your experience; detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity; enforce our Terms of Use; provide you with system or administrative messages, and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.

We may also use personal information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze Site usage, to improve our content and product offerings, and to customize the Site's content, layout, and services. These uses improve the Site and better tailor it to meet your needs, so as to provide you with a smooth, efficient, safe and customized experience while using the Site.

Please see our Terms of Use for information on what we do to account information when you terminate your account with us.

## What Information Do We Collect?

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information from you is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs, and to customize our service to make your experience safer and easier. We only collect personal information about you that we consider necessary for achieving this purpose.

In general, you can browse the Site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you become a registered User, we require you to provide various contact and identity information and other personal information as indicated on the relevant forms on the Site, and you are no longer anonymous to us. Where possible, on these forms we indicate which fields are required and which fields are optional. In addition, as you use the Site, you can from time to time enter or send to us personal information.

You always have the option to not provide information by choosing not to become a User or by not using the particular feature of the Site for which the information is being collected.

We also automatically track certain information about you based upon your behaviour on our Site. We use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behaviour to better understand, protect and serve you and our community. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on our Site or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on our Site or not), your computer browser information, and your IP address.

“Cookies” are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing our services. We use cookies to allow you to enter your password less frequently during a session, and we use data collection devices (such as Google Analytics), including cookies, on certain pages of the Site to help analyze our web page flow, measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety, to offer certain features that are only available through the use of a cookie and to allow us to provide information that is targeted to your interests.

Following your registration on the Site, you can review and change your information in your account area. If you disclose personal information on the Site and wish to have it removed, please contact us at the support contact information posted on the Site.

## Our Disclosure of Your Information

We will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to third parties without your explicit consent. The following describes some of the ways that your information may be disclosed in the normal scope of business to provide our services:

**Anonymized Aggregated Data.** We aggregate and anonymize data and use and disclose such information for a variety of purposes. However, in these situations, we do not disclose any information that could be used to identify you personally. 

**Public Areas of the Site.** All of your activities in the public areas of the Site will be identifiable to your User ID, and other people can see your published content. 

**Subsidiaries and Affiliates; Service Providers.** We may from time to time use the services of affiliates, subsidiaries and unrelated service providers in the operation of the Site, and may disclose personal information to them in the course of our use of their services. For example, we may use the services of third-party hosting companies to host the operation of the Site. This may involve the hosting of data, including personal information, on servers operated by those hosting companies. We take care to use only service providers that we believe are reputable and able to live up to our and your expectations, including about the handling of confidential information. 

**Legal Requests; Emergencies.** We cooperate with law enforcement inquiries and demands for information that are made under force of law. We are also cognizant of the need to address emergencies. Therefore, we may provide personal information in what we believe to be emergency situations, and we may provide personal information where required by statute, court order, legal process or lawful authority, and to our legal counsel. In some cases, personal information that we collect may be stored or processed outside of Canada, and may therefore be subject to the legal jurisdiction of those countries. 

We may also disclose personal information to the acquirer or its agents in the course of the sale of our business. If we do this, the disclosure will be subject to customary confidentiality agreements.

## Security

Appsession strives to protect your personal information. We make commercially reasonable effort to ensure the security of your personal information on our system. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot warrant the security of any information you transmit to us.

## Other Information Collectors

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties through the Site, different rules may apply to their use, collection and disclosure of the personal information you disclose to them. Since we do not control the information use, collection or disclosure policies of third parties, you are subject to their privacy policies. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

## Questions?

It is our goal to make our privacy practices easy to understand. If you have questions, concerns or if you would like more detailed information, please email our privacy officer at [contactus@affsession.com](mailto:contactus@affsession.com)
